avidian.com 2006-10-26

# Collaboration Software: Business Contact Manager, contact outlook sharing, client contact software, contact software, contact management software, Contact Managers, Contact Management System

---  
  
The privacy of individual visitor data is of primary importance to us. We work diligently to protect confidentiality, restrict transfer of personal data, incorporate technical safeguards and appropriate security policies, and identify privacy implications in new services.

We have created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and confidentiality. The policies described in this section apply to www.Avidian.com and are made available to make you aware of how we collect and use identifying information of visitors to our websites.

From time to time, we may need to change our privacy statement because of changes in our business, or in our attempts to serve your needs better. We’ll use reasonable efforts to publish any changes to our privacy statement. This site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such linked websites.  
  
“Identifying information” is exactly what it sounds like — it is information used to identify you as an individual visitor.

In situations where you haven’t provided anything to us, it is simply information such as your IP address or your browser type. This type of information allows us to do things such as identify and track problems on our server and find out how many people use one type of browser over another. In cases where you have provided us information by becoming a member of our site, filling out a form, signing up for our newsletters, or participating in a survey, the information may consist of items such as your name, e-mail address, company, etc. (whatever you’ve provided us). We use this type of information to help us personalize your experience on our website and send you your requested information.

Plus, we may selectively send out communications that may be of interest to you such as newsletters, special offers from Avidian and product announcements. You always have the choice of opting-out of receiving communications from us. Simply send us an email with unsubscribe in the subject to [info@avidian.com](mailto:info@avidian.com).

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and e-mail address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail. The friend may contact us to request the removal of this information from our database.

From time-to-time our sites request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level).

Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of our sites.  
  
We recognize your concern for security, and will continue to use reasonable efforts to establish secure connections with you and to limit access to databases containing personal information to authorized personnel only.

If you believe that we may not have your correct and current personal information, you may update your information any time by using the contact information below to inform us of changes in your personal information.

We’ll use reasonable efforts to honor your requests, but we appreciate your patience in allowing us a reasonable amount of time for processing. Please either:  
  
| 1. | E-mail [info@Avidian.com](mailto:info@Avidian.com) with corrections;  
---|---  
2. | Send postal mail to:  
| Customer Information Updates  
| Avidian Technologies LLC  
| 1500 112th Ave NE, Suite 101  
| Bellevue, WA 98004; or  
3. | Call 1-800-860-5534   
**Choice-Opt Out**  
You have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us by one of the following options:  
| 1. | E-mail [info@Avidian.com](mailto:info@Avidian.com) with corrections;  
---|---  
2. | Send postal mail to:  
| Customer Information Updates  
| Avidian Technologies LLC  
| 1500 112th Ave NE, Suite 101  
| Bellevue, WA 98004; or  
3. | Call 1-800-860-5534   
**Contact Us**  
Avidian Technologies, LLC is very committed to ensuring your privacy within our reasonable control. We want you to feel comfortable with your experience on our website and appreciate any feedback you may have to offer. If you believe we have not adhered to its privacy statement, if you would like to be deactivated from any of our lists, or if you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact [info@Avidian.com](mailto:info@Avidian.com).
